module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'On average, how many hours do squirrels spend sleeping every day?', 
      a: '8 hours', 
      b: '3 hours',
      c: '14 hours',
      d: '10 hours',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the animals below is NOT able to sleep while standing?', 
      a: 'Elephants', 
      b: 'Flamingos',
      c: 'Horses',
      d: 'White-Tailed Deer',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which animal regularly spends upwards of 20-22 hours a day sleeping?', 
      a: 'Sloth', 
      b: 'North American Opossum',
      c: 'Koala',
      d: 'Giant Armadillo',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'After giving birth, these dedicated mothers will go an average of 3 weeks without ANY sleep.', 
      a: 'Human', 
      b: 'Bottlenose Dolphin',
      c: 'Peregrine Falcon',
      d: 'African Leopard',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Sleeping an average of just 30 minutes a day, these animals have one of the shortest sleep requirements in the entire animal kingdom.', 
      a: 'Giraffe', 
      b: 'Pygmy Shrew',
      c: 'Sheep',
      d: 'Ring-Tailed Lemur',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Unihemispheric Slow-Wave Sleep (USWS) describes a state where some animals are able to:', 
      a: 'sleep with both eyes open', 
      b: 'greatly slow their heart rate',
      c: 'rest one half of the brain',
      d: 'teleport to Narnia',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of these animals is NOT considered a "True Hibernator"?', 
      a: 'Brown Bat', 
      b: 'Ground Squirrel',
      c: 'Woodchuck',
      d: 'Grizzly Bear',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What triggered humans to move from a biphasic sleep schedule (two periods of sleep), to monophasic?', 
      a: 'Industrialization', 
      b: 'Invention of the alarm clock',
      c: 'Street lighting',
      d: 'Lack of natural predators',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'For humans over the age of 18, what is the minimum recommended hours of sleep per night?', 
      a: '6', 
      b: '6.5',
      c: '7',
      d: '8',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the human record for the longest period without sleep?', 
      a: '15 days', 
      b: '6 days',
      c: '11 days',
      d: '9 days',
      answer: 'c'
    }
  ]
};